Letters to Santa is a tv movie, comedy, romance film directed by John Stimpson.
Young siblings use a magic pen from Santa to wish for
their parents to get back together.
Rebecca, played by Katie Leclerc.
Enrique, played by Rafael de la Fuente.
Camilla, played by Laura Cerón.
Candace, played by Mariana Paola Vicente.
Santa, played by Bates Wilder.
Mr. Hines, played by Lonnie Farmer.
A Muppets Christmas: Letters to Santa is a 2008 American
television special directed by Kirk R.
Thatcher featuring The Muppets in a Christmas mission to personally deliver three
letters to Santa Claus, accidentally diverted by Gonzo, to the North Pole.
The special aired on NBC on December 17, 2008.
The special, shot in Brooklyn and Midtown Manhattan, was released by
Walt Disney Studios Home Entertainment on DVD in 2009.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.